9: SOFTWARE DESIGN SPECIFICATION
10: Project Name (Code)
18: û Hanoi, Sep 2025 û
21: I. Record of Changes
22: *A - Added M - Modified D - Deleted
24: II. Software Design Document
25: 1. High Level Design
26: 1.1 Software Architecture
27: [The content of this section includes the overall architectural diagram which includes the sub-systems and/or components, the external systems (if any), and the relationships (communication messages) among them. You need also provide the explanation for each of the diagram components (modules, sub-systems, external systems, etc.)].
28: -
29: 1.2 Package Diagram
30: [Provide the package diagram for each sub-system. The content of this section including the overall package diagram, the explanation, package and class naming conventions in each package. Please see the sample & description table format below]
32: Package descriptions
34: 1.3 Database Design
35: [Provide the files description, database table relationship & table descriptions like example below]
37: 1.3.1 table_name1
38: [Provide brief description of the table here]
39: [Provide the detailed table fields description using below table format
 * PK~Primary Key; FK~Foreign Key; UN~Unique; NN ~ not null
41: 1.3.2 table_name2
42: à
